capacitor-plugin-safe-area
a capacitor plugin to get SafeArea info on Android and IOS
Version 5.0.0 published 2026-01-05 by zhuxian
Maintainers: zhuxian
Keywords: capacitor plugin native
https://npm.im/capacitor-plugin-safe-area

capacitor-secure-storage-plugin
Securely store secrets such as usernames, passwords, tokens, certificates or other sensitive information (strings) on iOS & Android
Version 0.13.0 published 2026-01-10 by martinkasa
Maintainers: martinkasa
Keywords: capacitor plugin native
https://npm.im/capacitor-secure-storage-plugin

@capawesome/capacitor-android-edge-to-edge-support
Capacitor plugin to support edge-to-edge display on Android.
Version 8.0.6 published 2026-02-19 by GitHub Actions
Maintainers: robingenz
Keywords: capacitor plugin native
https://npm.im/@capawesome/capacitor-android-edge-to-edge-support

@capacitor/filesystem
The Filesystem API provides a NodeJS-like API for working with files on the device.
Version 8.1.2 published 2026-02-13 by GitHub Actions
Maintainers: itschaced ionicjs jcesarmobile vmfo jpender dtarnawsky mark-ionic alexgerardojacinto os-pedrobilro harvdoggy jpender-os ndr kepatoto rui.mendes markemer capacitor-plugin-bot eric-ionic os-ruialves
Keywords: capacitor plugin native
https://npm.im/@capacitor/filesystem

capacitor-plugin-app-tracking-transparency
Capacitor plugin to request user authorization to access app-related data for tracking the user or the device.
Version 3.0.0 published 2025-12-20 by mahnuh
Maintainers: mahnuh
Keywords: capacitor plugin native
https://npm.im/capacitor-plugin-app-tracking-transparency

vue-cli-plugin-vuetify
Vuetify Framework Plugin for Vue CLI 3
Version 2.5.8 published 2022-09-13 by johnjleider
Maintainers: johnjleider kaelwd jsek andreyyolkin
Keywords: vuetify vuetify plugin vue-cli vue-cli vuetify vue-cli material vue-cli-3 vue-cli-3 vuetify vue-cli-3 material
https://npm.im/vue-cli-plugin-vuetify

@capacitor/cli
Capacitor: Cross-platform apps with JavaScript and the web
Version 8.3.0 published 2026-03-25 by capacitor-plugin-bot
Maintainers: itschaced ionicjs jcesarmobile vmfo jpender dtarnawsky mark-ionic alexgerardojacinto os-pedrobilro harvdoggy jpender-os ndr kepatoto rui.mendes markemer capacitor-plugin-bot eric-ionic os-ruialves
Keywords: ionic ionic framework capacitor universal app progressive web apps cross platform
https://npm.im/@capacitor/cli

@capacitor-firebase/messaging
Capacitor plugin for Firebase Cloud Messaging (FCM).
Version 8.2.0 published 2026-03-31 by GitHub Actions
Maintainers: robingenz
Keywords: capacitor plugin native
https://npm.im/@capacitor-firebase/messaging

capacitor-native-settings
Capacitor plugin to open native settings screens for android and iOS
Version 8.1.0 published 2026-03-17 by raphaelwoude
Maintainers: dennisameling raphaelwoude
Keywords: capacitor plugin native
https://npm.im/capacitor-native-settings

appsflyer-capacitor-plugin
AppsFlyer SDK plugin for Capacitor
Version 6.17.9 published 2026-03-25 by GitHub Actions
Maintainers: pazlavi dani-kozachkevich
Keywords: capacitor plugin native
https://npm.im/appsflyer-capacitor-plugin

@capacitor-mlkit/barcode-scanning
Capacitor plugin for ML Kit Barcode Scanning.
Version 8.0.1 published 2026-02-19 by GitHub Actions
Maintainers: robingenz
Keywords: capacitor plugin native
https://npm.im/@capacitor-mlkit/barcode-scanning

@capacitor-firebase/crashlytics
Capacitor plugin for Firebase Crashlytics.
Version 8.2.0 published 2026-03-31 by GitHub Actions
Maintainers: robingenz
Keywords: capacitor plugin native
https://npm.im/@capacitor-firebase/crashlytics

@capacitor/preferences
The Preferences API provides a simple key/value persistent store for lightweight data.
Version 8.0.1 published 2026-02-12 by capacitor-plugin-bot
Maintainers: itschaced ionicjs jcesarmobile vmfo jpender dtarnawsky mark-ionic alexgerardojacinto os-pedrobilro harvdoggy jpender-os ndr kepatoto rui.mendes markemer capacitor-plugin-bot eric-ionic os-ruialves
Keywords: capacitor plugin native
https://npm.im/@capacitor/preferences

@capacitor-firebase/analytics
Capacitor plugin for Firebase Analytics.
Version 8.2.0 published 2026-03-31 by GitHub Actions
Maintainers: robingenz
Keywords: capacitor plugin native
https://npm.im/@capacitor-firebase/analytics

@capacitor-firebase/authentication
Capacitor plugin for Firebase Authentication.
Version 8.2.0 published 2026-03-31 by GitHub Actions
Maintainers: robingenz
Keywords: capacitor plugin native
https://npm.im/@capacitor-firebase/authentication

@capgo/capacitor-social-login
All social logins in one plugin
Version 8.3.11 published 2026-04-08 by riderx
Maintainers: riderx
Keywords: capacitor plugin native social login google facebook apple twitter sso oauth oauth2
https://npm.im/@capgo/capacitor-social-login

@capacitor-community/media
Capacitor plugin for saving and retrieving photos and videos, and managing photo albums.
Version 9.1.0 published 2026-03-27 by nkalupahana
Maintainers: jcesarmobile vmfo maxlynch mhartington it_mike_s byrds rdlabo priyankpatel dwieeb stewan arielhernandezmusa jeepq start9keagan boosten nklayman ihadeed danielprrazevedo ckgaparajita jpender nhyatt pwespi epicshaggy thomasvidas robingenz diachedelic johnborges tobyas elylucas giodimiliaionic brownoxford mrbatista bazuka5801 hemang thegnuu pbowyer capcombot rui.mendes ndr alexgerardojacinto tafelnl os-pedrobilro dallasjames ryaa nkalupahana ionicjs multishiv19 peitschie damiantarnawsky harvdoggy capacitor-plugin-bot eric-ionic os-ruialves
Keywords: capacitor plugin native photo video albums
https://npm.im/@capacitor-community/media

@capacitor-community/file-opener
Capacitor File Opener. The plugin is able to open a file given the mimeType and the file uri.
Version 8.0.0 published 2025-12-25 by ryaa
Maintainers: jcesarmobile vmfo maxlynch mhartington it_mike_s byrds rdlabo priyankpatel dwieeb stewan arielhernandezmusa jeepq start9keagan boosten nklayman ihadeed danielprrazevedo ckgaparajita jpender nhyatt pwespi epicshaggy thomasvidas robingenz diachedelic johnborges tobyas elylucas giodimiliaionic brownoxford mrbatista bazuka5801 hemang thegnuu pbowyer capcombot rui.mendes ndr alexgerardojacinto tafelnl os-pedrobilro dallasjames ryaa nkalupahana ionicjs multishiv19 peitschie damiantarnawsky harvdoggy capacitor-plugin-bot eric-ionic os-ruialves
Keywords: capacitor plugin native
https://npm.im/@capacitor-community/file-opener

@capacitor-community/contacts
Contacts Plugin for Capacitor
Version 7.1.0 published 2025-12-24 by tafelnl
Maintainers: jcesarmobile vmfo maxlynch mhartington it_mike_s byrds rdlabo priyankpatel dwieeb stewan arielhernandezmusa jeepq start9keagan boosten nklayman ihadeed danielprrazevedo ckgaparajita jpender nhyatt pwespi epicshaggy thomasvidas robingenz diachedelic johnborges tobyas elylucas giodimiliaionic brownoxford mrbatista bazuka5801 hemang thegnuu pbowyer capcombot rui.mendes ndr alexgerardojacinto tafelnl os-pedrobilro dallasjames ryaa nkalupahana ionicjs multishiv19 peitschie damiantarnawsky harvdoggy capacitor-plugin-bot eric-ionic os-ruialves
Keywords: capacitor plugin
https://npm.im/@capacitor-community/contacts

@capacitor-community/in-app-review
Lets you prompt users to submit app store ratings and reviews without leaving your app - using platform native dialogs.
Version 8.0.0 published 2025-12-26 by jcesarmobile
Maintainers: jcesarmobile vmfo maxlynch mhartington it_mike_s byrds rdlabo priyankpatel dwieeb stewan arielhernandezmusa jeepq start9keagan boosten nklayman ihadeed danielprrazevedo ckgaparajita jpender nhyatt pwespi epicshaggy thomasvidas robingenz diachedelic johnborges tobyas elylucas giodimiliaionic brownoxford mrbatista bazuka5801 hemang thegnuu pbowyer capcombot rui.mendes ndr alexgerardojacinto tafelnl os-pedrobilro dallasjames ryaa nkalupahana ionicjs multishiv19 peitschie damiantarnawsky harvdoggy capacitor-plugin-bot eric-ionic os-ruialves
Keywords: capacitor plugin native
https://npm.im/@capacitor-community/in-app-review

